他相信道理簡單明瞭
One would believe in simple means
有人覺得也非不可能
Some would believe it possible
其他人則是漠不關心
Others feel it won't be seen
但沒人相信會有奇蹟
For none believe in miracles
有人用鑽石換碎石
Some give a diamond for a stone
有人用碎石換鑽石
Some give a stone for a diamond
有人守著自己的錢財
Some keep all things for their own
而也有人什麼都不說
And some remain in silence
純樸的古代，有位小女孩
There once lived a girl in a simpler time
皮毛與頭髮如晝夜般
with night-like hair and skin so white
不論她到哪，都對大家說
Wherever she went, everyone she'd tell
「似是己所有，爾可當己用」
"What'd appear as mine, 'tis thine as well"
她旅行四方，捐出她所有
So she went through the world, giving all she had
從來沒想過要拿回來
never feeling the need to claim it back
不論她到哪，大家都臣服
Everyone she'd meet would befall her spell
「雖是己所有，爾可當己用」
"What appears as mine, 'tis thine as well"
雖然她已時日不多
Counting the days of a shortening life
卻仍堅持大方作風
Living the ways of a nursery rhyme
哼聲有如鐘聲一般
Humming the tune of a ringing bell
雖是己所有，爾可當己用
What appears as mine, 'tis thine as well
他相信道理簡單明瞭
One would believe in simple means
有人覺得也非不可能
Some would believe it possible
其他人則是漠不關心
Others feel it won't be seen
但沒人相信會有奇蹟
For none believe in miracles
有人用鑽石換碎石
Some give a diamond for a stone
有人用碎石換鑽石
Some give a stone for a diamond
有人守著自己的錢財
Some keep all things for their own
而也有人什麼都不說
And some remain in silence